lecameleonhotel.com 2018-11-29

# Terms & Conditions | Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel

PRIVACY POLICY MAY CHANGE FROM TIME TO TIME AND ALL UPDATES WILL BE POSTED ON THIS PAGE. ANY QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS RELATED TO THE TERMS HEREIN SHOULD BE DIRECTED TO THE ATTENTION OF LE CAMELEON BOUTIQUE HOTEL AT THE FOLLOWING EMAIL: INFO@LECAMELEONHOTEL.COM  
CREATED ON: JULY 21, 2017

COPYRIGHT NOTICE  
Unless otherwise noted, all content on this website, lecameleonhotel.com, is copyrighted under Costa Rican law per the date of posting and is the property of Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel, All rights reserved. You are prohibited from using any of the content herein without the express written permission of Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. Copyright infringement will be prosecuted to the highest extent of the law.  
WARRANTIES DISCLAIMER  
No warranties are made with regard to the security of this website or any communications sent electronically to Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel.  
COLLECTED INFORMATION AND ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS  
When you send an e-mail communication, post a comment on this website, or request a service from Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel you’re also sending personally-identifiable contact information, such as your name, e-mail address, date of birth, credit card information, etc. Please note that as a professional website, Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel may log, record, track, or save the information you provide through the course of professional record-keeping or other personal, non-commercial use. Your information is never sold to third parties. Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel reserves the right to use the information collected from you through your use of this website for any non-commercial, academic, educational, or other not-for-profit uses. Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel may from time to time use the information you have provided to contact you about news or updates that Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel thinks you may be interested in. Again, by their nature, electronic communications are not always secure. It is your personal responsibility to be mindful of what you transmit over the Internet to Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel is not responsible for third party abuse of what you transmit through this website or when you send electronic communications to Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel.  
CONFIDENTIALITY OF INFORMATION SUBMITTED ELECTRONICALLY  
While Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel exercises reasonable efforts to maintain your confidentiality, electronic communications over the Internet are not always secure. Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel has no control over what third parties might do with electronically transmitted personal information. Please be mindful of that when using this website or e-mailing Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. It is not Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel’s responsibility to guarantee or warrant the security or confidentiality of any information you transmit electronically. Any information you have shared with Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel through your use of this website can be shared with organizations, individuals, affiliates, or others that Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel genuinely believes is reasonably necessary to:  
1\. Prevent imminent harm or risk of harm to yourself or to another.  
2\. Meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process, or governmental request, or  
3\. Investigate claims.  
THIRD PARTY LINKS  
From time to time, this website may link to other third party websites that are not operated or controlled by Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. These websites are linked for your convenience only, and do not imply endorsement of said links, and are not covered under this Terms of Use and Privacy Policy.  
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY  
Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel is not liable to you for any special or consequential damages that result from the use of, or the inability to use, any part of this website or the goods and services that may be offered on this website, or the performance of any services by Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. You indemnify and hold harmless Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel for any and all damages, losses, expenses, and costs, including reasonable attorneys’ fees, resulting from your use of this website and the application of information contained herein or disclosure of any of your personal information to Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel.  
AFFILIATE LINKS  
Some links within this site are affiliate links, meaning that Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel receives a small percentage of the proceeds from any sale transacted with the affiliate.  
COPYRIGHT  
All material is copyrighted by Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel, all rights reserved. You may not copy or post information from this website without express written permission from Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel. Infringers of Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel copyright will be prosecuted to the highest extent of the law.  
COOKIES AND ANONYMOUS IDENTIFIERS  
Through this website, you may receive cookies. Cookies are pieces of information that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record keeping purposes. Cookies are only sent back to the website that deposited them when a visitor returns to that site. Most web browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. You can, however, reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. Anonymous identifiers are random strings of characters that can be used the way cookies are used, for certain platforms like mobile devices where cookie technology is not available. By using this website, you acknowledge the receipt of cookies or anonymous identifiers and waive any rights to the contrary.  
INFORMATION COLLECTION, USE, AND SHARING  
Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.  
We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.  
Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

YOUR ACCESS TO AND CONTROL OVER INFORMATION  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or phone number given on our website:  
• See what data we have about you, if any.  
• Change/correct any data we have about you.  
• Have us delete any data we have about you.  
• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.  
SECURITY  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.  
Wherever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data), that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.  
While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The computers/servers in which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.  
DISCLAIMER  
Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel goes to great lengths to ensure that the information shared on or through this website is accurate, timely, and free of accidental typographical errors. In using this site, you agree that Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel is not responsible for any inaccuracies or errors that may occur herein stated on the website, its products, or its services.  
On occasion, testimonials may be presented concerning Le Cameleon Boutique Hotel products and services. These testimonials are real world examples, from actual clients/purchasers; however, they are presented for informational purposes only and do not represent or guarantee that you will have identical or similar results from your purchase of these products or services.
